Guide to the Ramón Hernández Tejano Music Collection
The Wittliff Collections
- Artist Files, 1922-2019, undated
  - Male Artist Files
    - Nick Martinez, undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Oscar Martinez, undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Oscar Martinez - Clippings, 1995-2011, undated (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Oscar Martinez - Audiovisual material, [2008], undated (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Oscar Calderon Martinez, 2016 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Richard Martinez, 2000, undated (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Roel Martinez, 1995, undated (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Sergio Martinez & Silveradoz, undated (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Tony Martinez, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Masizzo, 1997-2000, undated (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Masquerade, undated (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Ma$$ore, 2013, undated (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Masters of Love, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Eduardo Mata, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Geraldo Mata, Jr., undated (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Los Matadors, undated (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - Boni Mauricio, 2011, undated (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Los Mavericks de Emilio Vega, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Mazz - Photographs, 1983, 1987, undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Mazz - Concert and event publicity, 1989-1991, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Mazz - Albums, 1978-1995, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Mazz - Publicity, 1990-2001 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Mazz - Ramón Hernández material, 1985-1990, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Mazz - Discography research, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Mazz - Clippings (1 of 2), 1985-1998 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Mazz - Clippings (2 of 2), 2002-2018, undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Mazz - Magazines, 1989-2002 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Mazz - Audiovisual material, 1984-1994 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Charlie McBurney, 2003, undated (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Huey Meaux, 1996-2011, undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Medaya, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - La Medida, undated (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Bene Medina, 2009-2013, undated (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Javier Medina, undated (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Ramon Medina, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Los Medinas, undated (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Michael Mehl, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Joe Mejia, Jr., 1961-2001, undated (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Esteban Mendez, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Ramiro "Gallo" Méndez, undated (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Igo Mendoza, 2000, 2013, undated (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Igo Mendoza - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Willie Mendoza, 1989, undated (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Antonio Menendez, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Frank Mercado, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Metalis, undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Mex-Tex, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Mexican Stepgrandfather, 2010-2016, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Dan Michaels, undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Mickey and the Soul Generation, undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Midnight Mist, undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Midnight Sounds Band, undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Miguel y Miguel, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Mike and the Bel-Airs, 2014-2015, undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Los Milagros de Cristo, undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Millennium, undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Carlos Miranda, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Carlos Miranda - Clippings, 2000, 2013, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Brando Mireles, 1996, undated (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Mixed Company, 2013-2017, undated (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Modelo, undated (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Javier Molina, 1990, undated (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Simon "The Diamond" Molina, 1983, undated (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Los Monarcos, 2006, 2011, undated (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Ben Moncivais, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Francisco Monroy, 1990, undated (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Javier Monroy, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Monsanto Band - Clippings, 2007-2014, undated (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Monsanto Band - Audiovisual material, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Nicolás Montalvo, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Montana, 1989, undated (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Roberto Montana, undated (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Tony Montana, 1995, undated (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Montego, undated (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Leonard Montelongo, undated (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Roy Montelongo, 2009, undated (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Roy Montelongo - Clippings, 1990-2006, undated (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Roy Montelongo - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Arturo Montes y Ternura - Photographs, undated (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Arturo Montes y Ternura - Albums, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Arturo Montes y Ternura - Publicity, [1985], undated (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - Arturo Montes y Ternura - Ramón Hernández material, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Arturo Montes y Ternura - Clippings, 1986-1995, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Alex Montez, 1995, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Chente Montez, undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Victor Montez, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Montezuma, undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Ricardo Montoya, 1987, undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Moonstruck, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Jose Mora, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Ramon Gonzalez Mora, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Joe Morales Band, undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Joe A. Morales, undated (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Michael Morales, 1989-2013, undated (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Jose Morante, 2010, undated (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Antonio Moreno, undated (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Eddie Moreno, undated (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Jacinto Moreno, undated (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Jorge Moreno, 2003, 2007, undated (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Juan P. Moreno, 1995-2014, undated (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Mario Moreno, undated (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Ruben Moreno, undated (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Andres Ricardo Morin, 1999, undated (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Andres Ricardo Morin - Clippings, 1985-2015 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - George Morin, 1993, 2006, undated (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Joe Morin Band, undated (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Morning Star, undated (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Los Morros de Calif, undated (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Moses - Photographs, undated (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Moses, 1987, 2007, undated (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Muchachos de Lupito Banda, undated (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Al Muñiz, 2014, undated (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Balde Muñoz, undated (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Felipe "El Toro" Muñoz, undated (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Luis Alonso Muñoz, 1995, undated (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Musicians for Mexico, undated (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Mysterio, 1987, undated (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - MyZterio, undated (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Los Nahuatlatos, 2010-2014 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Nando and the Rhythm Aces, 2014, undated (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Bobby Naranjo y Direccion featuring Rene Serrata, undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Enrique "Flaco" Naranjo, 2000, undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Ricky Naranjo y Los Gamblers - Photographs, undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Ricky Naranjo y Los Gamblers, 2004-2011, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Ricky Naranjo y Los Gamblers - Audiovisual material, 2012 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Ruben Naranjo, 1998, undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Vick Nash, undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - David Navidad, 2000, undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Roel Nava, 2014, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Emilio Navaira - Photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Emilio Navaira - Photographs (2 of 2), undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Emilio Navaira - Photographs - Grammy Awards, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Emilio Navaira - Photographs - Market Square concert, undated (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Emilio Navaira - Photographs - Miller Outdoor Theater concert, undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Emilio Navaira - Photographs - Publicity photographs, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Emilio Navaira - Photographs - Mounted photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Emilio Navaira - Photographs - Mounted photographs (2 of 2), undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Emilio Navaira - Concert and Events - Concert flyers and publicity cards, 1989-2016, undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Emilio Navaira - Concert and Events - Tejano Night at Houston Livestock Show & Rodeo, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Emilio Navaira - Concert and Events - Tejano Music Awards, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Emilio Navaira - Albums, 1992-2001, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Emilio Navaira - Music videos, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Emilio Navaira - Publicity, 1989-2008 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Emilio Navaira - Advertisements, 1993, 1997, undated (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Emilio Navaira - Ramón Hernández material, 1985-2008 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Emilio Navaira - Clippings, 1990-1994 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Emilio Navaira - Clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Emilio Navaira - Clippings, 2000-2008 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Emilio Navaira - Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Emilio Navaira - Clippings, 2010-2011 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Emilio Navaira - Clippings, 2012-2018 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Emilio Navaira - Clippings, undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Emilio Navaira - Clippings, undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Emilio Navaira - Clippings collages, 1987-1990, undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Emilio Navaira - Magazines, 1990-1996 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Emilio Navaira - Magazines, 1996-2008, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Emilio Navaira - Magazine clippings, 1989-2002, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Emilio Navaira - Mounted clippings (1 of 2 ), 1987, 1990, undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Emilio Navaira - Mounted clippings (2 of 2), 1987, 1990, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Emilio Navaira - Audiovisual materials - Cassettes, 1989, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Emilio Navaira - Audiovisual materials - CDs, 1992-2005 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Emilio Navaira - Promotional material (1 of 2), undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Emilio Navaira - Promotional material (2 of 2), 2008, undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Raulito Navaira - Photographs, 2010, undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Raulito Navaira - Personal, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Raulito Navaira - Concerts and events, 2010-2016 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Raulito Navaira - Albums, 2009, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Raulito Navaira - The Raulito Show, 2011, undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Raulito Navaira - Clippings, 2000-2013, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Negami, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Jesus "Chuy" Negrete, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Willie Nelson, 2013, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Nemesis, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - The New Breed, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - New Definition, undated (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - The New Variety Band, undated (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - The Next Day, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - The Night Dreamers, undated (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Nightlife featuring Ruben Ramos, undated (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Nightwork, 1988, undated (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Los No. 2 Dinners, undated (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Los Nobles, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - La Noche, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Richard Noriega, undated (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Normandy, undated (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Nuestra Familia, undated (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Nueva Sensacion, undated (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Mario O., undated (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Joe Ojeda, undated (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Peter Ojeda, 2018 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Johnny Olenn, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Eddie Olivares, undated (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - David Olivarez, 2002, undated (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - David Olivarez - Clippings, 2006-2014, undated (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Fito Olivarez, 2000, undated (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Fito Olivarez - Clippings, 199-2013, undated (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Sigifredo Olivarez, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - Rey Olivas, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Brandon Olmos, 2011, 2016, undated (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Jesse Olvera, undated (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Gabriel Olveras, undated (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Omar y Los Rock-Itz, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - One Last Shot, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - George Ordonez, undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Organizacion Karizzia, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Benny Ornelas, 1989, undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Marcos G. Orosco y Extremo, undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - José Luis Orozco, 2015 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Marcos Orozco - Photographs, 2002, undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Marcos Orozco - Business cards, undated (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Marcos Orozco - Converts and events, 2001-2011, undated (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Marcos Orozco - Albums, 2001, undated (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Marcos Orozco - Ramón Hernández material, 2002, undated (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Marcos Orozco - Clippings, 2002-2014, undated (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Marcos Orozco - Audiovisual material, 2001, 2016 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Marcos Orozco - Promotional material, 2001, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Orquesta Nieto, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - La Orquesta Nueva, undated (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Mark Ortega, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Andrew Ortiz, undated (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Donald Ortiz, undated (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Froy Ortiz y Grupo Ellos, undated (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Gil Ortiz, undated (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Jesse Ortiz, 1988, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - George Ovalle, 2000-2001, undated (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Ben Ozuna, 2010, undated (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Jerry Ozuna, 2018 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Photographs (1 of 2), 1970-1983, undated (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Sunny Ozuna (2 of 2), 2009, undated (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Mounted images, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Publicity photographs, undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Personal, 2005, 2016, undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Concert and event publicity, 1996-2018, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Albums, 1981-1991, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Publicity, 1991, undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Business correspondence and records, 1986, 2016, undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Ramón Hernández material (1 of 2), 1986-2015, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Ramón Hernández material (2 of 2), 2000-2008, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Clippings, 1978-2018 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Clippings, undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Magazines, 1989-2017 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Los Pablos, [1972] (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Rupert Pacheco, undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Los Padrez, 1995, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Los Paisanos de Chalito Johnson, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Marvin Palacios, 1990, 2000, undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Rudy Palacios, 2009, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - The Paladins, undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Manuel Palafox, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Robert Palitos, 2015, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Los Palominos, 1999, undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Los Palominos - Publicity, 1985-2000, undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Los Palominos - Ramón Hernández material, 2001-2011, undated (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Los Palominos - Clippings, 1996-2016, undated (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - B.J. Pando, undated (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Roy Paniagua, undated (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Pantera, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Henry Parrilla, 2009-2018, undated (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Pasion, 2000, undated (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Los Pavos Reales, 2010-2014, undated (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Pazazz, undated (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Pee Wee, 2007-2013, undated (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Los Pekadores, 2014, undated (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Peligro, 2001, undated (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Los Perdidos, undated (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Domingo Peña, 1981-1996, undated (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Henry "Pepsi" Peña, 2016, undated (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Henry "Pepsi" Peña - Street Talk clippings, 2015-2018, undated (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Manuel Peña, undated (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Jesús "Chucho" Perales, 2000-2014, undated (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Joel Perales Family, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Rudy Perales, undated (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Alex Perez y Grupo Rezpeto, undated (Box 73, Folder 33)
    - Chris Perez, 1999-2015, undated (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - Chris Perez - Clippings, 1999-2015, undated (Box 73, Folder 35)
    - Chris Perez - Magazines, 1999, undated (Box 73, Folder 36)
    - David Perez, undated (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - Eddie Pérez, undated (Box 73, Folder 38)
    - Eddie Perez, 2015 (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - Eloy Perez, undated (Box 73, Folder 40)
    - Fidel Perez, undated (Box 73, Folder 41)
    - Frank Perez, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Gilberto Perez, 1993, 2011, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Henry Perez, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Jay Perez - Photographs, 1991, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Jay Perez - Personal, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Jay Perez - Concert and event publicity, 2002-2013, undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Jay Perez - Publicity, 1996, 1999, undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Jay Perez - Ramón Hernández material, undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Jay Perez - Clippings, 1990-2016 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Jay Perez - Clippings, undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Jay Perez - Magazines, 1995-2003 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Jay Perez - Audiovisual material, 2000-2001 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Jay Perez - Promotional material, undated (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Juan Alfredo Perez, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Neto Perez, undated (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Reno Perez, 1996-1997, undated (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Richard Perez, 2001, undated (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Ruben Perez, 2009, undated (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Tony Perez, 1989, undated (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Wild Bill Perkins, 2017-2018, undated (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Mike Pesina, 1992-1995, undated (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Phantacy, undated (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Piñata Protest, 2008-2017, undated (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Los Pinkys, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Ramón Piñon, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Joe Placencio y Maquina Alegre - Photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Joe Placencio y Maquina Alegre, 1999, undated (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - The Playboys, undated (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - The Players, undated (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - Plowboyz, undated (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Pobrezza, undated (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Pochimex, undated (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - El Poder de Texas, undated (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - J Posada, undated (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Joe Posada - Photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Joe Posada - Personal, 1990, undated (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - Joe Posada - Concert and event publicity, 1989-2013 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - Joe Posada - Album covers, 1993-1994 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - Joe Posada - Publicity, 1990, 2000, undated (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - Joe Posada - Ramón Hernández material, 1985-1988, undated (Box 74, Folder 40)
    - Joe Posada - Clippings, 1986-2017, undated (Box 74, Folder 41)
    - Potente, 1995, undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Potenzia, undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Power Band, 1986, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Power House, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Bob Prado, 1995, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - George Prado, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - The Premiers, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Presidente, undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Pression, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Pressure, undated (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - La Primera Band, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Project VI, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Project X, 1984, undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Promesa, undated (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - La Promesa, 1999, undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Propiedad Privada, 2015 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Proximo Sonido, undated (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Publio and the Valiants, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Pueblo, undated (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Pueblo Band, undated (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Bobby Pulido - Photographs, 1999, undated (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Bobby Pulido - Albums, 1995-2001, undated (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Bobby Pulido - Publicity, 1996-2002, undated (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Bobby Pulido - Clippings, 1995-2018, undated (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Bobby Pulido - Magazines, 1997-2013, undated (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Bobby Pulido - Audiovisual material, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Leonel Pulido, undated (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Roberto Pulido - Photographs, [1981], undated (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - Roberto Pulido - Personal, undated (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - Roberto Pulido - Concert and event publicity, 2013, undated (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Roberto Pulido - Album covers, 1974-1993 (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - Roberto Pulido - Publicity, 1990, undated (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - Roberto Pulido - Ramón Hernández material, 1986, undated (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Roberto Pulido - Clippings, 1986-2016, undated (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - Roberto Pulido - Magazines, 1993-2017, undated (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - Roberto Pulido - Audiovisual materials, 2001, undated (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Puro Party Band, undated (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - Chris Q., undated (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - The Q Brothers, undated (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - The Quarter Notes, 2005-2006, undated (Box 75, Folder 40)
    - Que Rico, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Quemado, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - A.B. Quintanilla, 2008-2017, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Abraham Quintanilla, 2009, 2012, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Elio Quintanilla, 1993-1997, undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Jerry Quinto, 1990, undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Ignacio "Nacho" Quiroz, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Phil Quiroz, undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Roger Rabbitt, 2010 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Rakim & Ken-Y, undated (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Ralph & the Cruisers, 2010, undated (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Ram and the Impalas, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Arnaldo "Mr. Falcon" Ramirez, 1979-1994, undated (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Augustin "El Guti" Ramirez - Photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Augustin "El Guti" Ramirez - Publicity, 1999, undated (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Augustin "El Guti" Ramirez - Concert and event publicity, 1987-2017 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Augustin "El Guti" Ramirez - Album covers, 1999, undated (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Augustin "El Guti" Ramirez - Ramón Hernández material, 1987, undated (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Augustin "El Guti" Ramirez - Clippings, 1962-2011, undated (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Gregg Ramirez, 2013 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Jorge Ramirez, undated (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Louis Ramirez, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Luis Ramirez, 2018, undated (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Raúl Ramirez, 1991, undated (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Tomas Ramirez, 1987, undated (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Alberto Ramon, 1990, undated (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Alberto Ramon, undated (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Alfonso Ramos - Photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Alfonso Ramos, 1988, 2011, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Andres Ramos y Fragancia, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Humberto "Beto" Ramón y Luna Llena, 1991, 1994, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Joe Ramos y Ellos, 1996-2011, undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Joe Ramos y Su Orquesta, undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - J.R. Ramos, 1991-1996, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Juan Ramos, 1995-2010, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Rey Ramos, 2008, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Ruben Ramos - Photographs, 2012, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Ruben Ramos - Personal, 2015, undated (Box 77, Folder 11)